what do i send my location to you
it's full of police in here
cleaning the barricade right here on the corner
it's full of police there
care
with the shit there
will give
go you're fine man
da is about two hundred and forty
two hundred and fifty brownies
I brought it more because I left it to volunteer teams
the staff that is important
we need energy
it's good
we live under donation today
which for you is the biggest need today
look in all sincerity
I could list
observe and learn a little more about perception
that he is already braking o
and my concern is
if i have this gas going through here
and it's already running leak
i have the concern from there
but for those who have strong thinking
the impossible is just a matter of opinion
and what came from this series that we created and
and built one hundred percent of the profit
that we managed to do
we wanted to ask you for the pix
and send the project there
bora there
I don't know if I can send you
what did you do to this account
hi dear
so if you bought a brownie there man
ended up collaborating for this moment to happen
then gratitude
immense for being part of this story
it's exactly what i have here in the bill guys
in the application because
it was 0 it was all
you must be wondering
and now
guy zeroed the box that will happen
tomorrow is the last day and get ready
for ideas or the latest in this series
hand tamo together
then you say something like that
that I speak
fucking
see you again
I want to see you another